This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
The White Beard Pirates have successfully pushed into the bay,
but a massive number of Marines still blocked the path to Ace.
The battle is heating up.
Why do any of them care? I deserve to die like this.
Why can't they see I'm not worth risking their lives for?
Please don't do this. Just stop. Just let me die like I'm supposed to.
Ace! You're my brother!
Please! Listen! That's enough!
Kuma! Look! It's me! Have you forgotten my face?
If you don't stop friendship being damned, I will fight back!
I don't know what kind of a history you two have, but it doesn't matter.
Trust me, Emporio Ivankov. There's really no use in talking to him as he is now.
Doflamingo, what are you saying? Is something wrong with him?
You're clearly a friend of Bartholomew Kuma's, so I doubt you'll take this well.
The man you knew as the tyrant Kuma is not the man you see before you now.
Because that man is dead.
Hate to tell you though, you're still not strong enough to beat me.
Dammit! You cheap jerk! Move that thing!
Get your filthy hands off him!
My body's smoke. How'd she hit me?
Wait a sec! Why did the pirate empress just save Straw Hand?
Hey Hancock, what the hell's wrong with you?
Don't tell me you're resigning from the warlords.
Shut your mouth! The screaming fury in my heart has rendered me deaf to your words.
How dare you pin my beloved down with your boorish club and threaten him!
You will die for your actions!
I've never felt this angry in my entire life!
I'll feed you piece by piece to wild animals!
The coochers hockey is overwhelming.
Kuma's transformation. Eva's blow of anger.
What the hell just happened?
I thought Hancock was supposed to be on our side!
No! Look! She's not saving him!
She's about to turn Straw Hat into something!
She's about to turn Straw Hat into stone!
I never stopped believing that you'd make it here alive and now, here you are.
No! Look! She's not saving him! She's about to turn Straw Hat into stone!
Take this. It's the key to your brother's handcuffs.
Wow! She's really doing a number on him! Straw Hat's frozen in place! He hasn't moved an inch! Did she turn him to stone?
Thanks, Hancock!
He... said... my name!
Huh?
Take this.
It's the key to your brother's handcuffs.
Wow, she's really doing a number on him.
Straw hat's frozen in place.
He hasn't moved an inch.
Did she turn him to stone?
Thanks, Hancock.
He said my name.
The touch of his hands.
They're strong, yet so kind.
Hancock.
Yay!
You're so awesome!
I can hug him forever!
I'll never forget this!
What a pal!
Thank you!
Oh, um, well, it's really no trouble at all.
I'm just glad I could help out.
Never mind me, though, Lupi.
Just go and save Ace.
Oh, yeah, right!
Thanks again!
No way!
He managed to defeat the Pirate Empress!
Unreal!
The Stare did nothing!
He's a beast!
He smothered her into submission!
I can't believe how easy he made it look!
Straw hat Luffy's unstoppable!
Oh, oh, Luffy!
Oh, Luffy!
My love!
You're too much!
Hold me like that again!
The warmth of his embrace still reverberates within my breast.
No, my entire body!
Could it be...
Perhaps...
This is...
What people call...
What they call marriage.
Snake princess!
Oh, my God!
Congratulations, sister!
Ah, there she is!
She's so pretty!
Oh, Luffy!
Best wishes, princess!
Oh, oh, Luffy.
I'll get you back!
Oh, oh, my D tamale!
My darling, you're beautiful.
I'm so happy!
Oh yeah? Better get used to it, baby.
Yes.
Hancock, baby.
Luffy, honey, baby!
Luffy, yes, this union was meant to be.
Between us lies a thread that links us together, an unbreakable bond that can't be cut.
It's a long, strong red string of fate, a mighty red serpent.
You ain't getting away, Straw Hat!
Curfume Fever!
Stay back, you fool! You shall not pass on my watch!
Geez, the Empress is really looking down on him.
Looking down so far, she started looking up!
Get out of my way, pirate.
You know what happens to people who betray the Navy?
Well, do you, woman?
I'll do whatever I like, and you will allow it. Because I'm beautiful.
Uh-huh? Uh-huh?
This is great! It's the exact thing I needed!
Hold on, Ace! I'm coming!
Impossible! Kuma is dead? Then who's that big guy standing behind you?
Stop spouting nonsense! You can't deceive me!
It's Eva!
And that big guy from before!
Eva, be careful! Don't let him get his paws on you! They're dangerous!
I'm alright. Kuma, get out of my way!
So, uh, are you guys friends or something?
We were, but he's not acting like himself.
I'm sure this is a lovely trip down memory lane for you, but I'm afraid the Kuma you know is no longer with us.
This is the new model.
New model? What do you think he's talking about?
He wants to get under my skin!
Yeah, okay. He's acting pretty different than usual right now, but he's still Kuma! Wake up, buddy! Hey!
Damn it all!
Then again, he's always been the quiet type.
Are you deaf or just stupid?
Trust me, it's no use trying to talk to him.
It happened just a few days ago.
Dr. Vegapunk, the government scientist, finally finished his modifications on Kuma.
Now he's the ruthless weapon of death he should have been from the start.
Ladies and gentlemen, the former Bartholomew Kuma!
Doc Vegapunk? Mods? What the hell are you talking about?
Kuma here volunteered to be a guinea pig in a study to build the ultimate human weapon.
Run by the government, of course.
First they modified his hands, then his legs.
Although his mind was still intact, they modified his body piece by piece.
Until he was no longer the same Kuma you know and love.
But that's nonsense!
Kuma always hated the government, you jerk!
As if he'd ever sacrifice himself for their stupid plan!
Hey, Kuma! Snap out of it! It's me!
Stop yelling. It's starting to get on my nerves.
I don't know what kind of deal he had with the government.
He was just fine a few days ago.
It's funny, but tragic. Before you know it, someone's gone.
In Kuma's case, he doesn't even realize he was ever human.
So the poor sap might as well be dead.
Now he's just a monster who the government has do their dirty work.
It's the latest, the greatest, pasa fiesta, PX0, your new old friend.
AHHHHH!
Ahhhhhh!
AHHH!
AHHHHH!
Ahhh!
AHHH!
AHHHHH!
A Drama Boy!
It's the gettin' Minnesota Iron Man breathe!
A
Kuma, what's the big idea?
You better stop shooting that laser crap at me right now!
Yeah, I remember.
We will never meet again.
Farewell.
Even then, he knew.
What's wrong, Kuma? Surely you recognize me?
That was spooky! Now where is he?
Hey, watch out, you guys! Get away!
Pad cannon.
Damn it, Kuma! That's enough!
You forgot me! But how about my face spectrum?
Ah!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Ah! This ring-a-bell?
How about this, galaxy wing?
Yee-haw!
How dare you attack my sweet, succulent crew of candy boys?
You can! I don't take unfashionable gestures lightly,
you conniving minks!
Vengeful kick!
Whoa!
Work it, boss!
I have met a lot of people!
Huh?
But no one forgets my face!
No one has ever forgotten my face in my entire life!
This mug is damn memorable!
Kuma!
If you want to forget who you are, that's your business!
But if you can't remember how dangerous the great Ivankov is,
then I will beat it into you!
So get ready, hon!
He is... pissed!
I'll take it from here!
Alright, my battling beauties, keep going and back Straw Boy up, okay?
Roger!
Okay, Straw Boy, let's get him!
Thanks! Good luck!
Come on, ladies! Get to the scaffold!
Huh?
All of a sudden, they just disappeared into the ice.
That doesn't make any sense unless Admiral Aokija used Ice Age again,
and I don't remember seeing him do that, do you guys?
Where'd they go?
Oh!
That's weird.
This is warm.
The ice?
All clear.
Okay.
Men, listen up.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Buggy is the greatest.
Yadda, yadda, yadda.
Buggy is amazing.
These are all things you guys have heard plenty of times.
Totally!
But I want to get the entire world chanting those words when their new pirate Savior makes his appearance!
Oh!
Excellent plan, your Buggyness!
Ugh.
Really?
No men!
Yadda!
Star Hat's gonna steal all my thunder!
Now commence Operation Mink, Captain Buggy the king of the pirates!
Anything is possible with me at the helm!
Yadda!
The whole world will be taken aback with my onslaught of awesomeness!
All of you, follow my lead and don't mess anything up!
Forward, you fools!
Yadda!
I question the efficacy of your latest strategy!
Young석-
Yadda!
Ya!
He's fast. Too fast. And strong. Quite a combination for someone that size.
Congrats on your escape from prison, Gator Boy.
So, did you enjoy the pool of blood during your stay?
Doflamingo. Keep out of my business or else. It's not your concern.
Just making small talk.
So, listen. I think we might make a good team.
Stop right there!
Yeah, you bitch!
Half clear, Straw Hat!
Nice one!
Haze!
Apologies, Shanks.
But I will not hold back against him.
Hey, I know him!
Hawkeye!
I wonder what is written.
Will my hand wipe his name from history?
Or perhaps his fortune shall spare him the fury of this black sword I wield.
Luffy's progress is halted by Dracule Mihawk, Warlord of the Sea. Cleaving apart the massive wall of ice surrounding the battlefield, one blow from Mihawk's sword will rend Luffy in two. The white-beared pirates counter with a swordsman of their own. But will his strength?
Be enough?
Will his strength be enough?
On the next One Piece, the great swordsman Mihawk, Luffy comes under the attack of the black sword. I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!